sfamelody.com 2019-01-20

# Privacy Notice : sfamelody.com, Your online shopping store

Your privacy is important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the information that we collect from you and how we use that information.

What information do we collect?

**Information Provided by Users and Other People**

Your account information. You provide your email to create an account or subscribe to our newsletter. If you refuse to provide such information, you may not be able to use the Services properly. When or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your contact information, such as your name, avatar, gender, address, telephone number and email address.

Your Information:

When you place an order, we request you to submit certain personal information such as your name, e-mail, shipping & billing address, credit card number and its expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status. We DO NOT share or give this information to any outside party with the exception of the necessary components in completing your order. Your credit card information will not be shared or used in any other manner than what is authorized by you, our customer. E-mail addresses are used solely for the purpose of communication between you.

Customer Support. You can provide us with information about your use of the Services, including your product information and how to contact you, so that we can provide customer support. For example, you can send an email that contains information about our device performance, application performance, and other issues.

**Device information**

Network and connection: We use the location-related information to tailor the Services to our users in different regions. Location-related information may be based on device location information (if the user grants approval to collect) or the user’s IP address.

Through Server Logs: A server log is a list of the activities that a server performs. DIVAINNER’s servers automatically collect and store in Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, the date and time of your request and referral URL and certain cookies that identify your browser or DIVAINNER account.

Cookies: Cookies are small text files that are sent to or accessed from your web browser or your computer’s hard drive. A cookie typically contains the name of the domain (internet location) from which the cookie originated, the “lifetime” of the cookie (i.e., when it expires) and a randomly generated unique number or similar identifier. A cookie also may contain information about your computer, such as user settings, browsing history and activities conducted while using the Services.

Analytic Cookies - These cookies allow us to collect data relating to your use of our sites, including the content on which you click while browsing on our sites, in order to measure the effectiveness and consumer interaction with the site and improve our sites over time. These cookies may be provided by our third-party analytics tool provider but are only used for purposes related to our sites.

Third-Party Information

How To Disable or Remove Cookies

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all our site features.

For more information on how to manage cookies on your browser, please access the appropriate link below:

Internet Explorer

Firefox

Chrome

Safari

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To process transactions: We use your personal information to process payments you make through the Services. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscription instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment Gateway Providers Database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, who are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date.
